
introname=INTRODUCTION

introcomics1=Professor Duriarti, a famous criminal, has escaped from prison. 
introcomics2=Meanwhile, life on the farm in Sunny Valley was good. 
introcomics3=But then Professor Duriarti came and seized the farm and captured the animals!
introcomics4=Through her network of informants, Supercow heard about the situation.
introcomics5=And dashed off to save the farm animals. Because after all, who knows how to save the farm better than Supercow?


